Woman on the Run is a thriller, tv movie film directed by Jason Bourque.
After surviving an attempt on her life, a reclusive mystery author discovers that her nanny has
stolen her identity, forcing her to go to extreme lengths to get her children back.
Nomi Gardner, played by Sarah Butler.
Greta March, played by Lindsay Maxwell.
Oscar, played by Matthew MacCaull.
Lyle, played by Josh Byer.
Detective Krantz, played by Karen Holness.
The Ritual is a 2017 British supernatural psychological folk horror film
directed by David Bruckner and written by Joe Barton.
Based on the 2011 novel of the same name by Adam Nevill, the film stars Rafe Spall, Arsher Ali, Robert James-Collier, and Sam Troughton
as four friends on a hiking trip through a Swedish old-growth forest, where they encounter an ancient evil presence.
Following its world premiere at the 2017 Toronto International Film Festival on 8
September, The Ritual was released by eOne in the United Kingdom on 13 October.
The film explores themes of infidelity, strong woman,
empowerment, stolen money, betrayal.
The tone is intense.